#### SENIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

# Vinícius Siqueira

I am a developer with over 7 years of experience, with almost 4 and a half years more focused on front-end web development using React JS. Proficient in UI Design and back-end, I have gained experience at major players, using current technologies such as Next.js, NestJS, and Tailwind.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer	Cadastra (M3 Ecommerce)	Aug, 2020 - Present (~4 years and 4 mont	ths)
<ul> <li>Implemented e-commerce sol</li> <li>Gained proficiency in various var</li></ul>	d LATAM (Argentina, Chile, Color Spanish communication skills. ed to major national retail players using agile methodology (Scrum).	ser experience. rderform, session, masterdata, services, whitelab mbia) projects, collaborating with Spanish-speaki s like Carrefour Brasil and RiHappy, integrating h. nt system for controlling distributed delivery	
	d <b>delivered</b> a notable project: a so	cript to handle a <b>large</b> volume of <b>requests</b>	
VTEX HTML CSS Sass JS Load Balancing Clean code Scr		ava (Spring) Gulp Webpack GShop Queues	
Full-stack Developer	friweb - Agência Digital	☐ Jan, 2019 - Jun, 2020 (~1 year and 5 mont	:hs)
<ul> <li>Achieved a level of independer and indirectly involved in.</li> <li>Developed payment gateway</li> </ul>	for the implementation and evolunce, commitment, and responsibility	ility to make decisions on projects I was directly latform, a mock exam platform for public tenders	
PHP HTML CSS JS JQue	ry Communication Leadership	Responsibility Independence	
Full-stack Developer	CEFET/RJ - Fábrica de Soft	ware 🛗 Jan, 2018 - Dec, 2018 (~11 mont	:hs)
<ul><li>Worked in design, creating log</li><li>Actively participated in the de</li></ul>	designers to serve the non-profit os and visual identities. velopment of a registration syste roject implementation process, for	em for a local event.	
PHP HTML CSS JS Figma	Agile Methodology Communic	cation Leadership	

### ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

## Bachelor's in Information Systems 📛 Jun, 2023 CEFET/RJ - UnED Nova Friburgo

Technical Degree in Information Technology

🛱 Dec, 2018 🛛 CEFET/RJ - UnED Nova Friburg
--